updatestar.com 2010-11-20

# UpdateStar - Simplify your software life

General

UpdateStar is serious about protecting your private sphere. This privacy policy statement concerns UpdateStar and the use and compilation of data. By using UpdateStar you confirm your agreement with the privacy policy outlined in this document.

Secure Compilation of Information

In order to make programs and updates available to you, UpdateStar must first analyse specific information from your computer and send it to our servers. Such information includes:

  *  Program Names 
  *  Version Numbers 
  *  Language Versions 
  *  Installation Dates 

as well as general information regarding your computer when executing program searches, updates and/or the retrieval of notifications:

  * Operating System 
  * Language Version 
  *  IP Address 
  *  Access Time 

All data are saved in a secure environment that is protected from unauthorized access, copying or use. In addition, all data are made anonymous by using a randomly created ID that in no way could by traced back to you. This ID is only used for identification purposes in conjunction with recurring requests and delivering notifications. No personal names or e-mail addresses are saved.

UpdateStar analyses data for the purpose of improving our UpdateStar service and for the purpose of offering interesting insights into software market developments and movements aggregated from the hundreds of thousands of anonymous users. These commercial offerings are used to refinance the UpdateStar project. To learn more about the services we offer, please visit our [Businesses Section](http://business.updatestar.com/).

UpdateStar may also conduct surveys from time to time to get your opinion on current products/services and other products/services that may be offered in future releases. At no time you will have to give us any personal information, as UpdateStar is a free and anonymous service for our users. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

Distribution of Your Data Due to Legal Requirements 

UpdateStar will distribute data to a third party without notifying you only when it is legally necessary or a substantiated claim has been made, for which UpdateStar is obliged to take action. Such instances requiring action would include:

  * Acting in compliance with UpdateStar's legal obligations to adhere to lawful business and operational practices 
  * Acting in protection or defense of UpdateStar's rights or property 
  * Acting in protection of the personal security of users of UpdateStar's products, websites or the general public. 

UpdateStar reserves the right to update this document from time to time to take into account feedback from companies and customers. UpdateStar recommends that you check this document on a regular basis to remain up-to-date on UpdateStar's privacy policy.

Your comments regarding this privacy policy are always welcome at UpdateStar. If you are of the opinion that UpdateStar is not adhering to the guidelines set out in this policy, please let us know. We will take your problem into consideration and, where necessary, find a solution.
